

BLAIR WARNER

blairthedesigner.com blairthedesigner@gmail.com

I am a User Experience and User Interface Designer who puts people first. With a background in graphic design and years of teaching experience, I am no stranger to problem solving. I love to make meaningful experiences and hope to make people's lives a little better. I also enjoy drawing, practicing Japanese, and I have an unhealthy addiction to denim.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE UX/UI DESIGNER

Blair the Designer - Seattle, WA 8.2016 - present Providing clients with user experience and interface design solutions that meet both user needs and business goals. Working with product managers, developers and other designers to create user-centered designs on web, iOS and Android platforms.

INSTRUCTIONAL ASSISTANT (UX DESIGN)

General Assembly - Seattle, WA 11.2016 - 2.2017 Assisted Instructors with curriculum creation, lesson planning, and student evaluations. Planned cross-functional hackathon.

ENGLISH TEACHER

Ibaraki, Saitama and Tokyo, Japan 4.2006 - 3.2008 / 4.2011 - 3.2016 Worked in a total of 22 different elementary and junior high schools in the Greater Tokyo area. Collaborated with teachers to make lessons and activities tailored to different grade and skill levels. Acted as a cultural ambassador for my students. Participated in school functions and after school activities.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / LETTERPRESS PRINTER

Bell'Invito Letterpress Studio - Dallas, TX 2.2009 - 8.2009 Worked with clients, marketers, designers and printers to develop custom, couture letterpress stationery. Was also responsible for the creation of web graphics for the company website, and file preparation for die creation. Operation of 19th-century letterpresses for printing and die-cutting, as well as assembly of stationery.

ASSISTANT GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Standard Deluxe, Inc. - Waverly, AL 5.2005 - 2.2006
Worked with clients, designers and printers to create designs for silkscreen printing. Worked with web developers to created web graphics and inputted data for the company website and web store.

EDUCATION

UX Design Immersive

General Assembly - Seattle, Washington 2016

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design

Auburn University - Auburn, Alabama 2000 - 2005

SKILLS

Affinity Diagrams Comparative Analysis Competitive Analysis Concept Maps Heuristic Evaluation Information Architecture Navigation Personas Prototype Site Maps Sketching Storyboarding Task Analysis User Flows User Journeys **User Scenarios User Stories** Wireframes

TOOLS

Axure
Balsalmiq
Illustrator
InDesign
Invision
Office
Omnigraffle
Photoshop
Sketch